{
  "Session183617":{
    "Question0":[
      {
        "Question":"Early bird or night owl?",
        "Answer":"Night owl"
      }
    ],
    "Question1":[
      {
        "Question":"Are you more of a dog person or a cat person?",
        "Answer":"Cat person"
      }
    ],
    "Question2":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have edible spaghetti hair that regrows every night or sweat maple syrup?",
        "Answer":"Maple syrup sweat"
      }
    ],
    "Question3":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question4":[
      {
        "Question":"Do you prefer coffee or tea?",
        "Answer":"Tea"
      }
    ],
    "Question5":[
      {
        "Question":"Are you someone who enjoys cooking at home or dining out?",
        "Answer":"Dining out"
      }
    ],
    "Question6":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather live in a world where everyone's emotions are visible above their heads or where everyone's thoughts are audible?",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question7":[
      {
        "Question":"Are you someone who enjoys cooking at home or dining out?",
        "Answer":"Dining out"
      }
    ],
    "Question8":[
      {
        "Question":"Are you someone who enjoys cooking at home or dining out?",
        "Answer":"Dining out"
      }
    ],
    "Question9":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather live in a world where everyone's emotions are visible above their heads or where everyone's thoughts are audible?",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question10":[
      {
        "Question":"Speak every language fluently but only in rhymes or communicate with animals but only through interpretive dance?",
        "Answer":"Talk with animals through dance"
      }
    ],
    "Question11":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have x-ray vision but can't turn it off or have the ability to see 10 seconds into the future but can't change it?",
        "Answer":"See 10 seconds into the future"
      }
    ],
    "Question12":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have a pet dragon or a pet unicorn?",
        "Answer":"Pet dragon"
      }
    ],
    "Question13":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the ability to talk to plants or control the weather?",
        "Answer":"Control the weather"
      }
    ],
    "Question14":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question15":[
      {
        "Question":"Are you someone who prefers to plan everything in advance or go with the flow?",
        "Answer":"Going with the flow"
      }
    ],
    "Question16":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question17":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question18":[
      {
        "Question":"Always have to whisper or always have to shout?",
        "Answer":"Always shout"
      }
    ],
    "Question19":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather live in a bustling city or a quiet countryside?",
        "Answer":"Countryside"
      }
    ]
  }
}{
  "Session183617":{
    "Question0":[
      {
        "Question":"Eat a spoonful of wasabi every day or a whole raw onion every week?",
        "Answer":"Raw onion every week"
      }
    ],
    "Question1":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the ability to talk to plants or control the weather?",
        "Answer":"Control the weather"
      }
    ],
    "Question2":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question3":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have fingers as long as your legs or legs as long as your fingers?",
        "Answer":"Legs as long as fingers"
      }
    ],
    "Question4":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the power of super strength or super speed?",
        "Answer":"Super speed"
      }
    ],
    "Question5":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question6":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the ability to fly but only at walking speed or run as fast as a cheetah, but only for 10 seconds at a time?",
        "Answer":"Short but fast run"
      }
    ],
    "Question7":[
      {
        "Question":"Book or movie?",
        "Answer":"Movie"
      }
    ],
    "Question8":[
      {
        "Question":"Book or movie?",
        "Answer":"Movie"
      }
    ],
    "Question9":[
      {
        "Question":"Movie night in or night out at the theater?",
        "Answer":"Theather"
      }
    ],
    "Question10":[
      {
        "Question":"Have a permanently itchy nose or a constantly dripping nose?",
        "Answer":"Constantly dripping nose"
      }
    ],
    "Question11":[
      {
        "Question":"Game night or karaoke night?",
        "Answer":"Karaoke night"
      }
    ],
    "Question12":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question13":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have a tail like a cat or ears like a rabbit?",
        "Answer":"Rabbit ears"
      }
    ],
    "Question14":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have a tail like a cat or ears like a rabbit?",
        "Answer":"Rabbit ears"
      }
    ],
    "Question15":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather travel to the past or the future?",
        "Answer":"Future"
      }
    ],
    "Question16":[
      {
        "Question":"Speak every language fluently but only in rhymes or communicate with animals but only through interpretive dance?",
        "Answer":"Talk with animals through dance"
      }
    ],
    "Question17":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question18":[
      {
        "Question":"Always have a clown following you or always have a chicken riding on your shoulder?",
        "Answer":"Chicken on shoulder"
      }
    ],
    "Question19":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ]
  }
}{
  "Session183618":{
    "Question0":[
      {
        "Question":"Always have to whisper or always have to shout?",
        "Answer":"Always shout"
      }
    ],
    "Question1":[
      {
        "Question":"Beach vacation or mountain retreat?",
        "Answer":"Mountain retreat"
      }
    ],
    "Question2":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have a teleportation ability or time travel ability?",
        "Answer":"Time travel"
      }
    ],
    "Question3":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question4":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have a teleportation ability or time travel ability?",
        "Answer":"Time travel"
      }
    ],
    "Question5":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the ability to talk to plants or control the weather?",
        "Answer":"Control the weather"
      }
    ],
    "Question6":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have a teleportation ability or time travel ability?",
        "Answer":"Time travel"
      }
    ],
    "Question7":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the power of super strength or super speed?",
        "Answer":"Super speed"
      }
    ],
    "Question8":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the power of telekinesis or mind reading?",
        "Answer":"Mind reading"
      }
    ],
    "Question9":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question10":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question11":[
      {
        "Question":"Test2",
        "Answer":"No2"
      }
    ],
    "Question12":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question13":[
      {
        "Question":"Do you like to read fiction or non-fiction books?",
        "Answer":"Non-Fiction"
      }
    ],
    "Question14":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have x-ray vision but can't turn it off or have the ability to see 10 seconds into the future but can't change it?",
        "Answer":"See 10 seconds into the future"
      }
    ],
    "Question15":[
      {
        "Question":"Pizza or pasta?",
        "Answer":"Pasta"
      }
    ],
    "Question16":[
      {
        "Question":"Always have a clown following you or always have a chicken riding on your shoulder?",
        "Answer":"Chicken on shoulder"
      }
    ],
    "Question17":[
      {
        "Question":"Summer or winter Olympics?",
        "Answer":"Winter olympics"
      }
    ],
    "Question18":[
      {
        "Question":"Game night or karaoke night?",
        "Answer":"Karaoke night"
      }
    ],
    "Question19":[
      {
        "Question":"Speak every language fluently but only in rhymes or communicate with animals but only through interpretive dance?",
        "Answer":"Talk with animals through dance"
      }
    ]
  }
}{
  "Session183618":{
    "Question0":[
      {
        "Question":"Wear a cape everywhere you go or always wear a top hat?",
        "Answer":"Top hat"
      }
    ],
    "Question1":[
      {
        "Question":"Pizza or pasta?",
        "Answer":"Pasta"
      }
    ],
    "Question2":[
      {
        "Question":"Are you a fan of sweet or savory snacks?",
        "Answer":"Savory"
      }
    ],
    "Question3":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question4":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have fingers as long as your legs or legs as long as your fingers?",
        "Answer":"Legs as long as fingers"
      }
    ],
    "Question5":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have unlimited money but live in a world without books or have unlimited books but live in a world without money?",
        "Answer":"Unlimited books, no money"
      }
    ],
    "Question6":[
      {
        "Question":"Beach vacation or mountain retreat?",
        "Answer":"Mountain retreat"
      }
    ],
    "Question7":[
      {
        "Question":"Wear a cape everywhere you go or always wear a top hat?",
        "Answer":"Top hat"
      }
    ],
    "Question8":[
      {
        "Question":"Do you like action-packed movies or romantic comedies?",
        "Answer":"Romantic comedies"
      }
    ],
    "Question9":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question10":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question11":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather travel to the past or the future?",
        "Answer":"Future"
      }
    ],
    "Question12":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the power of telekinesis or mind reading?",
        "Answer":"Mind reading"
      }
    ],
    "Question13":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question14":[
      {
        "Question":"Beach vacation or mountain retreat?",
        "Answer":"Mountain retreat"
      }
    ],
    "Question15":[
      {
        "Question":"Do you prefer coffee or tea?",
        "Answer":"Tea"
      }
    ],
    "Question16":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the ability to fly or be invisible?",
        "Answer":"Invisibilty"
      }
    ],
    "Question17":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question18":[
      {
        "Question":"Do you prefer coffee or tea?",
        "Answer":"Tea"
      }
    ],
    "Question19":[
      {
        "Question":"Book or movie?",
        "Answer":"Movie"
      }
    ]
  }
}{
  "Session183618":{
    "Question0":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have endless summer or perpetual winter?",
        "Answer":"Winter"
      }
    ],
    "Question1":[
      {
        "Question":"Test2",
        "Answer":"No2"
      }
    ],
    "Question2":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the ability to breathe underwater but only in a bathtub or be able to talk to plants but only during a full moon?",
        "Answer":"Talk to plants during full moon"
      }
    ],
    "Question3":[
      {
        "Question":"Wear a cape everywhere you go or always wear a top hat?",
        "Answer":"Top hat"
      }
    ],
    "Question4":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question5":[
      {
        "Question":"Summer or winter Olympics?",
        "Answer":"Winter olympics"
      }
    ],
    "Question6":[
      {
        "Question":"Early bird or night owl?",
        "Answer":"Night owl"
      }
    ],
    "Question7":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question8":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the ability to breathe underwater but only in a bathtub or be able to talk to plants but only during a full moon?",
        "Answer":"Talk to plants during full moon"
      }
    ],
    "Question9":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question10":[
      {
        "Question":"Eat a spoonful of wasabi every day or a whole raw onion every week?",
        "Answer":"Raw onion every week"
      }
    ],
    "Question11":[
      {
        "Question":"Are you a fan of sweet or savory snacks?",
        "Answer":"Savory"
      }
    ],
    "Question12":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather live in a bustling city or a quiet countryside?",
        "Answer":"Countryside"
      }
    ],
    "Question13":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have an extra arm or an extra leg?",
        "Answer":"Extra leg"
      }
    ],
    "Question14":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question15":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have unlimited money but live in a world without books or have unlimited books but live in a world without money?",
        "Answer":"Unlimited books, no money"
      }
    ],
    "Question16":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather travel to the past or the future?",
        "Answer":"Future"
      }
    ],
    "Question17":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have endless summer or perpetual winter?",
        "Answer":"Winter"
      }
    ],
    "Question18":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather explore outer space or the depths of the ocean?",
        "Answer":"Ocean"
      }
    ],
    "Question19":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ]
  }
}{
  "Session183618":{
    "Question0":[
      {
        "Question":"Do you like to read fiction or non-fiction books?",
        "Answer":"Non-Fiction"
      }
    ],
    "Question1":[
      {
        "Question":"Always have to sing instead of speak or dance instead of walk?",
        "Answer":"Dance instead of walking"
      }
    ],
    "Question2":[
      {
        "Question":"Early bird or night owl?",
        "Answer":"Night owl"
      }
    ],
    "Question3":[
      {
        "Question":"Wear a cape everywhere you go or always wear a top hat?",
        "Answer":"Top hat"
      }
    ],
    "Question4":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question5":[
      {
        "Question":"Always have to whisper or always have to shout?",
        "Answer":"Always shout"
      }
    ],
    "Question6":[
      {
        "Question":"Test2",
        "Answer":"No2"
      }
    ],
    "Question7":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question8":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have x-ray vision but can't turn it off or have the ability to see 10 seconds into the future but can't change it?",
        "Answer":"See 10 seconds into the future"
      }
    ],
    "Question9":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have endless summer or perpetual winter?",
        "Answer":"Winter"
      }
    ],
    "Question10":[
      {
        "Question":"Do you enjoy listening to music while working or prefer silence?",
        "Answer":"Silence"
      }
    ],
    "Question11":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question12":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question13":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have the power of super strength or super speed?",
        "Answer":"Super speed"
      }
    ],
    "Question14":[
      {
        "Question":"Pizza or pasta?",
        "Answer":"Pasta"
      }
    ],
    "Question15":[
      {
        "Question":"Have the ability to teleport but always end up 10 feet above the ground or be able to breathe underwater but only in a bathtub?",
        "Answer":"Breathe underwater"
      }
    ],
    "Question16":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question17":[
      {
        "Question":"Movie night in or night out at the theater?",
        "Answer":"Theather"
      }
    ],
    "Question18":[
      {
        "Question":"Test1",
        "Answer":"No1"
      }
    ],
    "Question19":[
      {
        "Question":"Would you rather have unlimited money but live in a world without books or have unlimited books but live in a world without money?",
        "Answer":"Unlimited books, no money"
      }
    ]
  }
}